Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series II: Events, Projects, and Services
  - c. 1986-2014(Second Donation)
    - Youth Related Programming
      - HIV, c. 2009 (Box 62, Folder 38)
        Also Includes brochures on sexuality by Planned Parenthood, PGLAG, National Mental Health Association
      - Queer Homeless Youth, c. 2008 (Box 62, Folder 39)
      - LGBT Reports/Articles, 1999-2003 (Box 62, Folder 40)
        Homelessness, intersexuality, school legislation, Massachusetts same-sex marriage (most undated)
      - Marriage Info, 1999-2004 (Box 62, Folder 41)
      - Info for Families, c. 2005-2009 (Box 62, Folder 42)
      - LGBT Online High School, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 43)
      - Domestic Abuse Brochures, Undated (Box 62, Folder 44)
      - School Rights/Safety, Undated (Box 62, Folder 45)
        ACLU Prom Night Rights, Trevor Project Educator Resources Guide
      - Sexual Health, Undated (Box 62, Folder 46)
      - Safer Sex Brochures, Undated (Box 62, Folder 47)
      - Pregnancy Brochure, Undated (Box 62, Folder 48)
      - LGBT & Tobacco, Undated (Box 62, Folder 49)
      - Straight Allies, Undated (Box 62, Folder 50)
      - Suicide/Depression, Undated (Box 62, Folder 51)
      - LGBT Terms, Undated (Box 62, Folder 52)
      - Transgender Awareness, Undated (Box 62, Folder 53)
        Education for trans allies/families
      - Trans Youth Resources, Undated (Box 62, Folder 54)
      - Trans Resources, 2010-2011 (Box 62, Folder 55)
      - Gender Nonconforming Kids, 2006, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 56)
      - Gender Identity Disorder (GID) Info, Undated (Box 62, Folder 57)
        Includes Standards of Care (Fifth Version)
      - Trans/Gender Nonconforming Youth, Undated (Box 62, Folder 58)
      - Boxes 63-65 are RESTRICTED
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 69)
      - Youth Program, November 2011 (Box 63, Folder 70)
        Youth Program folders contain sign-in sheets for groups and drop-in hours, volunteer time sheets, calendars, events
      - Youth Program, October 2011 (Box 63, Folder 71)
      - Youth Program, September 2011 (Box 63, Folder 72)
      - Youth Program, August 2011 (Box 63, Folder 73)
      - Youth Program, July 2011 (Box 63, Folder 74)
      - Youth Program, June 2011 (Box 63, Folder 75)
      - Youth Program, May 2011 (Box 63, Folder 76)
      - Youth Program, April 2011 (Box 63, Folder 77)
      - Youth Program, March 2011 (Box 63, Folder 78)
      - Youth Program, February 2011 (Box 63, Folder 79)
      - Youth Program, January 2011 (Box 63, Folder 80)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, December 2010 (Box 63, Folder 81)
        Includes calendar and contact sheet
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, November 2010 (Box 63, Folder 82)
        Includes calendar
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, October 2010 (Box 63, Folder 83)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, September 2010 (Box 63, Folder 84)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, August 2010 (Box 63, Folder 85)
        Includes contact sheet
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, July 2010 (Box 63, Folder 86)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, June 2010 (Box 63, Folder 87)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, January-May 2010 (Box 63, Folder 88-92)
      - Youth Program Calendars, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 93)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, May-December 2008 (Box 63, Folder 94-101)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, January-April 2008 (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
      - Youth Program Calendars (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, January-December 2007 (Box 64, Folder 6-17)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, January-December 2006 (Box 64, Folder 18-29)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, January-December 2005 (Box 64, Folder 30-41)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, January-December 2004 (Box 64, Folder 42-52)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, March 2003 (Box 64, Folder 53)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, May-July 2003 (Box 64, Folder 54)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, August-December 2003 (Box 64, Folder 55-59)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 60)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms (1), 2002 (Box 64, Folder 61)
      - Youth Program Intake Forms (2), 2002 (Box 64, Folder 62)
      - Youth Center Sign In/Out (1), 2008 (Box 64, Folder 63)
      - Youth Center Sign In/Out (2), 2008 (Box 64, Folder 64)
      - Youth Group Attendance, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 65)
      - Young Adult Group Attendance, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 66)
      - Specialty Groups Attendance, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 67)
      - Youth Group Calendars, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 68)
      - Drop In Hours Attendance, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 69)
      - Young Adult Group, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 70)
        Mission Statement, attendance, meeting summaries
      - Youth Group Attendance, 2004-2005 (Box 64, Folder 71)
      - Young Adult Group Attendance, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 72)
      - Youth Group Attendance, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 73)
      - Youth/Young Adult Group, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 74)
        Attendance, meeting summaries
      - Sign-in Sheets - Youth Group, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 75)
      - Intakes, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 76)
      - Youth Intake Forms, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 77)
      - Meeting Notes, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 78)
      - Meeting Notes, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 79)
      - Youth Intake Forms, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Youth Group Sign-in Sheets, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Youth Group Evaluations, 1999-2000 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Youth Group Sign-in Sheets, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Notes, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Meeting Notes, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Youth Group, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
        Meeting notes and sign-in sheets
      - Youth Intake Index Cards, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Youth Group, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Youth Intake Index Cards, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Youth Group, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Resources, c. 1999 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        Hotlines, local organizations, hand-outs
      - Support for Gay Youth, 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        Mainly news clippings and copies of news clippings
      - Gay Youth Empowerment, 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Growing Up Gay, c. 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Parents Support, Undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Local Youth Agencies, c. 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Youth Bibliography Information, c. 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Youth Articles, c. 1993-1995 (Box 66, Folder 8)
        Journal articles, newsletters, and copies of information sheets.
      - Catalogs for Gay Pride Products, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Transgender and Intersex Information, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Youth Agencies - Other Cities, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Mailing Lists, 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 13)
        For other related organizations
      - Chuck Collins - from the Downtown United Presbyterian Church, c. 1992-1994; FD-62 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Advertising, c. 1993 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Referral Network, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Lighthouse Status Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Sample Organizational Structures and Rules, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Outgoing Correspondence (Chuck Collins), 1992, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - For Better or Worse (comic strip), 1993 (Box 66, Folder 19)
        Character on the comic strip comes out.
      - Teen Suicide, 1995-2001 (Box 66, Folder 20)
        Articles and information sheets
      - TASS, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 21)
        Grant materials
      - Youth Surveys, Undated (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - Safe Schools Project, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - LGBT Youth Centers, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - Body Image, c. 2002 (Box 66, Folder 25)
      - Youth - Empty Closet, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - Internships, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 27)
      - Flyers for Presentations, Undated (Box 66, Folder 28)
      - Budget Narrative for Grant Proposal, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 29)
      - Grant Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 30)
      - Dwellings, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 31)
        Design proposal for youth center
      - Dwellings, 2005; CD-2441 (Box 66, Folder 31)
      - Community Resource Exchange Packet, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 32)
      - Congressional Resource Services Information Pack on Grants, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 33)
      - Health Services, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 34)
      - Grant Funding Opportunities, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 35)
      - Frameline: Film and Video Catalog, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 36)
      - City Newspaper, February 17-23, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 37)
        An issue dedicated to "Coming out, Coming of Age"
      - GLSEN Materials, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 38)
      - Gay Elders: Articles, Undated (Box 66, Folder 39)
      - 4 Phone Message Books, 1999-2002 (Box 66)
      - Bill Kelly/Youth MH, Undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Youth Program Folders, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 24-141)
        Restricted until 2093.
      - Youth Program materials, 2012 (Box 69, Folder 9-11)
    - Parents of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) Files
      - AIDS/HIV Resources, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Articles, 1995-1998 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - "Answers to Your Questions" PFLAG & Family Resources, c. 1987-1991 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - "Be Yourselves" PFLAG Literature for Youth, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Catholic, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Coming Out/Holidays, Undated (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - Common Myths, c. 1986 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - Definitions from Gender Community, Undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - Evaluations - PFLAG Meeting, Undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - Expectations, Family - Non-conformists, FAG, 1993-1997 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - Heterosexual Questionnaire, History, Homosexuality - 15 Questions, Homophobia, 1991-1998 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - History - Clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - Ideas, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Is Homosexuality a sin?, 1992-1997 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - "Journey to Gratitude," PFLAG, Undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - Justice Report V.1, no. 1, Fall 1995; Mel White, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Library, Lobbying, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 40)
      - Marriage, 1995-1997 (Box 43, Folder 41)
      - Media, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Meetings info and by-laws. Rochester PFLAG, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Minutes, Rochester PFLAG, 1993-1998 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - National, 1994-1997 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - "The Next Step", Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - October: Lesbian Gay History Month and NCOD Outreach Survey, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - People of Color, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - PFLAG Do's and Don'ts., Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Policy, 1989-1994 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Materials translated into Portuguese, Undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Products, 1992-1997 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Reading List, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Reflections of a Gay Catholic, Undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Reparative Therapy, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Resources, 1995-1998 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - School Psychologists, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - School, 1992-1995 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Speakers Bureau, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Speaking for Ourselves Study Guide, Undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Stationary, Undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Twilight of the Golds, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Tips & Tactics - Newsletter, 1995-1998 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1994-1997 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Trevor: Study Guide, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Voter Registration, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - What the Bible Says About Homosexuality, 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Who is Killing Whom?, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Why Ask Why, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - You Can Help/Youth, 1991-1997 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - Youth and Homosexuality, 1991-1997 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - PFLAGpole "Don't Forsake Homosexual Who Want Help.", 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - APA On Sexual Orientation, Undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Action Alert (ENDA), 1995 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Bibliographies, Undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Bisexual Resources, Undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Can we Understand?, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - P-FLAG Rochester Brochure, Undated (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Bible Cartoons, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - All in the Family Cartoon, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - About Our Children, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Expectations, Undated (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - Suggested Reading, Undated (Box 44, Folder 42)
      - Fortune Mag, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - Gays at Work, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 44)
      - GAGV Pamphlets, Undated (Box 44, Folder 45)
      - Getting Personal, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - Heterosexual Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Homosexuality - 15 Questions, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 48)
      - Homophobic Attitudes, Undated (Box 44, Folder 49)
      - Homophobia Indicators, Undated (Box 44, Folder 50)
      - Ignorance NOT Bliss, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 51)
      - Is Homosexuality a Sin?, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 52)
      - My Lesbian Mom, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 53)
      - Common Myths, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 54)
      - Mom, You'd Better Sit Down, Undated (Box 44, Folder 55)
      - Parents Live In Closets Too, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 56)
      - P-FLAG Newsletter Nov/Dec, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 57)
      - P-FLAG Rochester Newsletter, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 58)
      - P-FLAG Newsletter Jul/Aug, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 59)
      - P-FLAG Newsletter May/June, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 60)
      - P-FLAG Newsletter Jan/Feb, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 61)
      - P-FLAG Newsletter, 1995-1998 (Box 44, Folder 62)
      - Newspaper Articles, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 63)
      - P-FLAG Acts Up, Undated (Box 44, Folder 64)
      - New York State Reps, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 65)
      - Gay Civil Rights-5 Myths, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 66)
      - Schools, 1991-1996 (Box 44, Folder 67)
      - Speakers Evaluations, Undated (Box 44, Folder 68)
      - P-FLAG Recommended Readings, Undated (Box 44, Folder 69)
      - "Straight or Gay" Parents Mag., 1988 (Box 44, Folder 70)
      - Opening the Straight Spouse's Closet, 1992, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 71)
      - Supporting Our Gay Loved Ones, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 72)
      - Schools, 1993-1997 (Box 44, Folder 73)
      - P-FLAG Rochester, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 74)
      - "Can We Understand?" A Guide for parents prepared by NYC PFLAG, Statement of Purpose, Undated (Box 44, Folder 75)
      - Rochester PFLAG Newsletters, Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 76)
      - Fliers - Homosexuality: Ministry & Families, Common Myths about Gays and Lesbians, Parents Live in Closets Too, Parents FLAG Do's & Don’t's, Undated (Box 44, Folder 77)
      - P-FLAG Logo/Stationary, Undated (Box 44, Folder 78)
      - P-FLAG Donation Thank -You Letter Template, Undated (Box 44, Folder 79)
      - Heterosexual Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 80)
      - PFLAG Pamphlets, Stickers, Homosexuality & The Bible, 1979, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 81)
      - Strategic Planning, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 82)
      - Myths about Gays and Lesbians, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 83)
      - Lobbying Rules & Limitations for PFLAG Chapters, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 84)
      - Articles from Media - PFLAG In the News/Coming Out Stories, 1993-1999 (Box 44, Folder 85)
      - PFLAG Rochester Newspaper clippings, comics, pamphlets, 1993-2001 (Box 44, Folder 86)
      - Pamphlets, stickers, questionnaires, coming out to your parents, 1994, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 87)
      - PFLAG Newsletters, Affiliation Packets, 1994-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Straight Spouses, 1994, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Rochester Monthly Meeting Sign-In, 1994-1998 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Bisexuality - PFLAG resource packet & Newsweek Issue, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - PFLAG Organizational Material, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - PFLAG - Board Minutes, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Administrative Calendar, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - How-To Manual for PFLAG Chapters, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - PFLAG Misc. - Chapter Roster, Bylaws, Bisexuality Resource Packet, 1996, 2001, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Mailing List, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Tips & Tactics Newsletter, 1996-2002 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - What the Bible Says About Homosexuality, PFLAG Pamphlet, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Pamphlets about Sexuality & Coming Out, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - PFLAG Rochester Newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - PFLAG Staff-National, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - PFLAG Board Meeting notes, guide for parents, grant proposal, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - PFLAG Meeting and Event Info, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - PFLAG seal, Undated; MU-2304 (Box 31)
    - Lilac Rainbow Alliance for the Deaf (LRAD) Files
      - Business Meeting Minutes, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 14-16)
- Series III. Empty Closet
  Files often include correspondence, news clippings, newsletters, fliers, advertisements and press releases. Other forms of material have been noted.
  - Alphabetical Subject Files 1971-1984 (First Donation)
    - A-F
      - Abortion, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Abzug, Bella, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - ACLU- Gay, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Action for a Better Community annual report, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Advertising, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - A Gay Bibliography, 6th ed., Mar. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - "A Guide to STD's For Gay Men" pamphlet, Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - AIDS Hotline information, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - American Psychiatric Association, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Amnesty International, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - "Andrew Holleran Interviews Felice Picano", 1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Ann Landers- gay issues, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Anti-discrimination bill media (?), 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Anti-gay, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - The Atlanta Report, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Bettering Ram: Organ of the Rochester Rams, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Berg, Ensign Vernon, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Betty Fairchild/Nancy Hayward article, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Bibliographies, 1974, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Bill Benet, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Bisexuality, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Bisexuality, 1973, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Body Politic (gay journal) information, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Books Bohemian Catalog, #9, Mar. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Boycotts, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Brown, Dr. Howard, 1973, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Bryant, Anita, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Buffalo, 1971,1975 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Byrne, Lady Mayor, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Campus Times clippings- University of Rochester, 1972, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Capitol Hill, v.1 no.3, Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Carter, President Jimmy, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Child custody and visitation rights, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - Children's rights, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Choice News, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Christopher Street, 1976, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - City parking maps, downtown, Undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Classic Concepts III, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - Clergy- supportive, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - Colvin, Earl, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Cooperative living, Undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Costanza, Midge, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Couples- marriage, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - Dade County, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Daryl Clemens- articles on hustling/male prostitution, 1980? (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - "Dear Anita", Undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Dignity- Boston newsletter, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Dignity, Inc. newsletter, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Dignity/Integrity newsletter, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Dignity-Integrity Rochester, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Dignity-Integrity Rochester brochures, Undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Disabled, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Election results, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Employment, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - ERA, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Event flyers, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - "Facts of Being Gay" pamphlet, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Fair Campaign Law- codes, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Families & amp; Friends of Gays (includes numerous NYC POG newsletters), 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Families & amp; Friends of Gays of Rochester newsletter, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Rochester Parents of Gays group information, 1974,1976,1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Family Protection Act, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Family Protection Act, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Finger Lakes Equal Justice Association, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Fletcher Brothers, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - F. Brothers- direct mailing on consensual sodomy ruling, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Free Libertarian Party, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - G-L
      - GAA question #8: Religion, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - GAGV Media, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Gay advertisement information (marketing), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Gay alcoholics, 1980? (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Gay and lesbian alcoholics, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Gay arts, 1973, 1978? (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Gay bars, 1978? (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Gay baths, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Gay books, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Gay books and reviews, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Gay book reviews, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Bay books bibiliographies, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Gay business, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - The Gay Christian, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Gay Community News, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - GCN fire press release, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Gay democrats, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Gay films, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Gay health, 1971, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Gay information booklet, Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Gay legislation- general, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Gay legislation- bills, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Gay/Lesbian Media Directory Worldwide, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Gay lifestyles, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Gay magazine articles, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Gay magazines- reviews, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Gay marches, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - "Gay Men and STDs" brochure, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - "Gay Men's Health Crisis Hotline Protocol", Feb. 1984 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Gay men's liberation, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Gay news articles, 1976,1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Gay Nurses Alliance, 1977,1981 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Gay Olympic Games, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Gay parents, 1973,1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Gay parents, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Gay/Police Relationship Reports, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Gay political power, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Gay Report, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Gay rights, 1971-1981 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Gay Rights National Lobby lobbying information, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 57-58)
      - Gay Rights National Lobby News, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 59-60)